fueluptowin.ca 2016-03-24

# Privacy - Fuel up to WIN 2016

Privacy

**As per Rule 6 in theOfficial Rules: PRIVACY:** Game Sponsor will be collecting personal data about you for the Game and for purposes of the game to validate winning submissions. By entering the Game, you consent to the collection of personal data and you grant Game Sponsor permission to send winner notification to you. No such personal data will be transferred or sold to any third party except in the following circumstances 

  * When you give us permission to do so;
  * When in good faith we believe the law requires it;
  * Under limited circumstances specifically described to you when we collect the information, such as in the rules of games, sweepstakes or other promotions;
  * To our respective agents for data processing purposes, our respective professional advisors and promotional and marketing agencies, provided that such agents, professional advisors and promotional and marketing agencies are restricted from using the information for any purpose other than as described in these Official Rules.
  * To Game Sponsor’s agents for data processing purposes, or to its professional advisors and promotional and marketing agencies, provided that such agents, professional advisors and promotional and marketing agencies are restricted from using the information for any purpose other than as described in these Official Rules.

Game Sponsor may match aggregated, statistical user information to parameters established by third parties, without releasing any personally identifiable information. Game Sponsor may share aggregate information with trading partners, co-branded locations, participating sponsors and advertisers; however, this aggregated information will not contain personally identifiable information. Any requests for access to the information that entrants have supplied, or to update or rectify such information, must be made in writing by sending a self-addressed envelope with your request to: "Fuel up to Win, c/o P.O. Box 3009, M.I.P., Markham, ON, L3R 6G4".

Federated Co-operatives Limited (FCL) respects your right to privacy and will use your personal information only to conduct the Contest and for the purpose as described in the Official Rules. Information collected is used solely to administer the Contest and is not sold, rented, or loaned to any third parties. No correspondence will be entered into except with selected entrants. FCL will handle the entrant’s personal information in accordance with its privacy policies and practices, which can be accessed by contacting the FCL privacy officer at [privacy@fcl.ca](mailto:privacy@fcl.ca); and in accordance with applicable laws. By completing and submitting a contest entry form you consent to the collection use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes stated herein.View the Privacy Policy included in our Official Rules, specific to our Contest. 

Security

To maximize security for our visitors, we employ a GeoTrust certificate recognized by Microsoft Internet Explorer (8+), Google Chrome (14+), Apple Safari (5+) and Mozilla Firefox (9+) browsers that use 128-bit encryption ("Compatible Web Browsers"). Older browsers will still create a secure SSL connection at 40, 56 or 128 bits depending on the precise browser version. Encryption is a means of scrambling information for transmissions, in this case, between your PC and our web-site. Information that is encrypted (Scrambled) at one end is decrypted (descrambled) upon receipt at the other end. 128-bit encryption is the strongest, most secure form of encryption that is generally available in Internet browsers today. 40-bit encryption is the basic minimum standard that is prevalent in most browser products. Compatible Web Browsers with 128-bit encryption can be downloaded by clicking on their respective icons. 

No purchase necessary. Contest is open to legal residents of Ontario, Manitoba, Saskatchewan, Alberta, British Columbia and the Northwest Territories who are the age of majority in their province or territory of residence. Correct answer of a mathematical skill-testing question required to redeem any prize. Void elsewhere and where prohibited. Contest ends April 21, 2016 at 11:59 pm PT. 1 in 6 tickets reveals a prize or discount. For complete contest rules, entry and eligibility requirements, or how to receive a ticket without purchase, see Official Rules. Prizes may not be exactly as shown. 

Any trade-marks used are the property of their respective owners. CO-OP® and CO-OP® design are registered trade-marks of TMC Distributing Ltd., Saskatoon, SK, S7K 3M9. CO-OP® design is a registered trade-mark of TMC Distributing Ltd. THE MARKETPLACE™ is a trade-mark of Federated Co-operatives Limited. Saskatoon, SK, S7K 3M9.
